convertstring.com 2018-12-25

# Convert String - Privacy Policy

You'll be pleased to know that our website uses industry standard encryption to protect your information when you transmit it over the internet. When SSL is enabled (click the padlock at the top of the page) you will notice a little padlock icon in your browser that shows that the connection is a secure one between your computer and our servers. With SSL enabled you can be sure that you are indeed connecting to ConvertString.com and that the data is secure during transmission. 

## Our Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to ConvertString.com is important to us. 

At ConvertString.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit ConvertString.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your information, personal or otherwise to third parties. 

### User Information

We collect no personal information, except arguably your [IP address](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address), which is stored within the server log files (see below). 

### Submitted Information

We collect no submitted information. All information sent to us for conversion using our conversion tools is simply converted and sent back to you. We do not use temporary files to store this information during conversion, we use no permanent storage whatsoever. 

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on ConvertString.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googles DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ('interest based targeting'). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses 'non personally identifiable information'. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

AdSense Privacy Policy provided by [JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)
